(Raj:)-Shall I wait?
-Yes, please.
(Sheldon:)How may I help you?
(Raj:)I've reconsidered your offer
to let me work with you.
(Sheldon:)For me.
(Raj:)Yes, for you.
(Raj:)I do, however, have a few conditions.
(Raj:)First, at all times, I am to be treated
as a colleague and an equal.
(Raj:)Second, my contributions shall be noted
in published materials.
(Raj:)Third, you are never allowed to lecture me
on Hinduism or my Indian culture.
(Sheldon:)I'm impressed, Raj.
(Sheldon:)Those are very cogent
and reasonable conditions.
(Raj:)-Thank you.
-I reject them all.
(Raj:)Then you leave me no choice.
(Raj:)I accept the job.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry.
I believe you've misunderstood.
(Sheldon:)I'm not giving you the job.
(Sheldon:)I'm simply affording you the opportunity
to apply for it.